https://ittc.co.uk/privacy-policy/

English
Arabic Chinese (Simplified) Czech English French German Italian Polish Spanish Turkish
Privacy policy
This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information
we collect about you when you use this website or enrol on a course at the school. Topics include:
Who are we?
What information do we collect about you?
How will we use the information about you?
Who will we share your information with?
Where do we store your information?
How to contact us
Who are we?
BEET Language Centre is an English language teaching and English language teacher training centre. The teacher training centre operates under the name of ITTC (International Teaching and Training Centre). ITTC is part of BEET, and in this privacy policy is included under the name ‘BEET’.
What information do we collect about you?
We collect information about you when you make an enquiry or enrol with us. We also collect information as part of your stay at the centre – information about your academic progress, your attendance and any disciplinary issues. We also collect information when you complete questionnaires using paper forms or digital tools such as SurveyMonkey. We collect website usage information using cookies. We are the ‘controllers’ of the data we collect: this means it is BEET who decides what to collect, and how to store it and use it, not another organisation. If you have booked your course at BEET with another organisation, they will collect the personal information needed to enrol you at the school, and are also ‘controllers’ of that information.
How will we use the information about you?
We collect information about you to enrol you on your course, manage your course and, if you agree, to email you about other courses and opportunities we think may be of interest to you. We also collect information about exam results and teachers’ assessments to help us assess how well we are meeting the needs of students, and to show our school inspectors.
Who will we share your information with?
If you booked your course at BEET with another organisation, we may share some information with that organisation. If you are aged 16-17 years, we will also inform your parents or legal guardians if we are worried about your welfare or if they ask for reports on your progress. If you were sponsored by an organisation or embassy, we will share with that organisation or embassy any information which is relevant to their sponsorship of your course. We will also share information if we need to respond to requests for information from school inspectors or the UK government.
BEET will not share your information with any organisations other than those above.
Where do we store your information?
Digital information about you is stored in the UK and is encrypted and password-protected. Any paper records are kept in secure locations with access restricted to authorised need-to-know users.
Access to your information and correction
You can ask for a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email us at the following address admin@beet.co.uk, or write to us at BEET Language Centre, Nortoft Rd, Bournemouth BH8 8PY, England. You will not have to pay for this, unless you make lots of requests. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is wrong.
How long we keep your information
We only keep information which we need to manage your course, or which you agree to give us to help us with our publicity. When we no longer need to keep your data, we will remove it. If you would like us to remove data about you and your course, you can contact us at admin@beet.co.uk, but please note that we may need to keep some data for legal reasons or school inspectors.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to monitor and analyse how visitors use the website and to make reports on website activity. For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org . You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not work well as a result.
Other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
Changes to our privacy policy
We check our privacy policy regularly and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 22 May 2018.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you by emailing admin@beet.co.uk or writing to BEET Language Centre, Nortoft Rd, Bournemouth BH8 8PY, England.
This privacy notice has been adapted from the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) website: https://ico.org.uk/media/for-organisations/documents/1625136/good-and-bad-examples-of-privacy-notices.pdf
Try a taster day!
Are you thinking of a new direction, have you considered teaching English?
Our Teaching Taster day is ideal if you’re thinking about teaching English as a career, if you’re on a gap year or if you want to go travelling and earn some money abroad.
Find out more
Contact Us
English Language Teacher Training Since 1984
Contact UsDownload Brochure
Close this module
Would you like a FREE OTRC course module? Buy one or more modules & we'll give you a FREE one!Don’t miss the chance to get your FREE module! Bookings must be received before 31st December!View CourseNo thanks, I’m not interested!This website uses cookies to improve your experience. By using this website you agree to our privacy policy. I UnderstandPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
